Monster Heroes is a comedy film directed by Danny Cistone.
A film maker documents the trials and tribulations of four classic monster
descendants and their ability to live among a human society.
Matt, played by Danny Cistone.
Neil Stein, played by Brent Tarnol.
Draco, played by Carson Aune.
Cansha, played by Alvaro Orlando.
Sam, played by Michael Blum.
Brenda Stein, played by Angela Pupello.
Monster Hunter is a 2020 monster film written, directed, and produced by Paul W.
Anderson, based on the video game series of the same name by Capcom.
The film stars Milla Jovovich in her sixth outing
together with Anderson, her husband.
The other cast members include Tony Jaa, T.I., Meagan Good,
Diego Boneta, Josh Helman, MC Jin, and Ron Perlman.
The film follows Artemis (Jovovich) and her loyal soldiers when they are transported to a new world,
where they engage in a battle for survival against enormous monsters with incredible powers.
A film adaptation based on the series had been in
conception since 2012 by director Paul W.
The film was formally announced by Capcom in October 2018, with
production starting that month with Constantin Film.
Principal photography on the film began on October 5, 2018 and was
completed on December 19, 2018, in Cape Town, South Africa.
Monster Hunter was released to theaters during the COVID-19 pandemic, by Sony Pictures Releasing (excluding Germany,
China and Japan), opening in China on December 4, 2020, and in the United States on December 18, 2020.
The film was a box office bomb, having only grossed $47.9 million worldwide against a production budget of $60 million and received mixed
reviews, with praise for its action sequences, visual effects, and musical score, but criticism for its direction and editing.
It received a nomination at the 19th Visual Effects Society Awards, in the
category Outstanding Effects Simulations in a Photoreal Feature.
The tone is lighthearted.